{
  "status": "SUCCESS",
  "data": {
    "testId": "oihq2eo9h1029921-210-20112",
    "questions": [
      {
        "questionId": "b28af948-db8b-465e-92e6-3d42534c4533",
        "question": "The company's ___ approach to product development ___ customer feedback at every stage, ___ user satisfaction and ___ a loyal consumer base.",
        "questionType": "text",
        "answerType": "options",
        "options": ["Incorporated", "User-centric", "Enhancing", "Cultivating"],
        "correctAnswer": [
          "User-centric",
          "Incorporated",
          "Enhancing",
          "Cultivating"
        ]
      },
      {
        "questionId": "6e6534ea-260a-4c26-96fd-f830b27601fb",
        "question": "The ___ musical performance ___ elements from various genres, ___ the audience with its unique sound and ___ critical acclaim from industry experts.",
        "questionType": "text",
        "answerType": "options",
        "options": ["Captivating", "Eclectic", "Garnering", "Blended"],
        "correctAnswer": ["Eclectic", "Blended", "Captivating", "Garnering"]
      },
      {
        "questionId": "7186e3da-0384-460a-af19-5a3984758e78",
        "question": "The scientist's ___ research on quantum computing ___ new possibilities for data processing, ___ traditional limitations and ___ the way for groundbreaking technological advancements.",
        "questionType": "text",
        "answerType": "options",
        "options": ["Pioneering", "Paving", "Overcoming", "Opened up"],
        "correctAnswer": ["Pioneering", "Opened up", "Overcoming", "Paving"]
      },
      {
        "questionId": "10cbe3c2-13bb-4973-a794-18bf309b0791",
        "question": "The ___ implementation of machine learning algorithms in medical diagnostics ___ early detection of diseases, ___ treatment outcomes and ___ the workload of healthcare professionals.",
        "questionType": "text",
        "answerType": "options",
        "options": ["Improving", "Reducing", "Enabled", "Revolutionary"],
        "correctAnswer": ["Revolutionary", "Enabled", "Improving", "Reducing"]
      },
      {
        "questionId": "71ffe41e-8732-48e6-87f2-f84ea07eb060",
        "question": "The ___ security breach at the tech giant ___ millions of users' data, ___ concerns about online privacy and ___ calls for stricter regulations.",
        "questionType": "text",
        "answerType": "options",
        "options": ["Raising", "Massive", "Prompting", "Compromised"],
        "correctAnswer": ["Massive", "Compromised", "Raising", "Prompting"]
      },
      {
        "questionId": "48b9b4bd-5c2c-4c25-92c0-ce453b14e8d7",
        "question": "The ___ educational reform ___ a more inclusive curriculum, ___ equal opportunities for all students and ___ the overall quality of public schooling.",
        "questionType": "text",
        "answerType": "options",
        "options": ["Comprehensive", "Enhancing", "Implemented", "Promoting"],
        "correctAnswer": [
          "Comprehensive",
          "Implemented",
          "Promoting",
          "Enhancing"
        ]
      },
      {
        "questionId": "ed5e6e2d-8408-406e-be32-777ac26460e2",
        "question": "The company's ___ commitment to sustainability ___ eco-friendly practices across all departments, ___ its carbon footprint and ___ a model for corporate responsibility.",
        "questionType": "text",
        "answerType": "options",
        "options": ["Implemented", "Setting", "Unwavering", "Reducing"],
        "correctAnswer": ["Unwavering", "Implemented", "Reducing", "Setting"]
      },
      {
        "questionId": "936eccaa-2f3b-4322-a3d3-ceabf2219dc5",
        "question": "The ___ implementation of artificial intelligence in healthcare ___ patient outcomes, ___ the workload of medical professionals and ___ new avenues for personalized treatment.",
        "questionType": "text",
        "answerType": "options",
        "options": ["Opening", "Improved", "Gradual", "Reducing"],
        "correctAnswer": ["Gradual", "Improved", "Reducing", "Opening"]
      },
      {
        "questionId": "d78effdf-88ab-4667-8115-3bfb2baa0a24",
        "question": "The ___ festival ___ artists from diverse backgrounds, ___ cultural exchange and ___ a platform for emerging talents to showcase their work.",
        "questionType": "text",
        "answerType": "options",
        "options": [
          "Providing",
          "Brought together",
          "Promoting",
          "International"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": [
          "International",
          "Brought together",
          "Promoting",
          "Providing"
        ]
      },
      {
        "questionId": "2d08ec76-a253-4f34-bc45-e12ef21b78fb",
        "question": "The ___ implementation of smart city technologies ___ urban efficiency and sustainability, ___ quality of life for residents and ___ a model for future urban development.",
        "questionType": "text",
        "answerType": "options",
        "options": ["Enhancing", "Improved", "Providing", "Widespread"],
        "correctAnswer": ["Widespread", "Improved", "Enhancing", "Providing"]
      }
    ]
  },
  "message": "Questions fetched successfully",
  "activity": {
    "id": "3c576049-9ea9-4b5c-9fb7-4b316adaaaa0",
    "userId": "c6ad08a5-67ac-4a4d-aa3a-16d7fe91d51c",
    "type": "VERSANT_CATEGORY_TEST",
    "coinType": "DEDUCTED",
    "coins": 20,
    "description": "Used Versant Category Test",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-10T06:42:21.041Z"
  }
}